Guide to the Records of Director of Academic Program Review, Barnett Hamberger 1972-2003 RG 9.7 RG 9.7
New York University Archives
- Series I
  - NYSED 1.1 Basic Student Charges, 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - NYSED 2D, 2E, 2F College of Dentistry, 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - NYSED 2H Enrollment of Impaired Students, 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - NYSED 2.1, 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - NYSED 2.4 Opening Fall Enrollment, undated (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - NYSED 2.4B PT UG Degree- Credit Enrollment, undated (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - NYSED 2X.1 College W/S Actuals, 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - NYSED 3, 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 37)
  - NYSED 4.1, 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 38)
  - NYSED 5 College and U Libraries, 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - NYSED 7, 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 40)
  - NYSED 8, 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 41)
  - IPEDS--EF1 Enrollment by Racial/Ethnic, 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 42)
  - IPEDS F1, 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 43)
  - IPEDS R1 Residence of 1st-Time Student, 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 44)
  - ITALNET, 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 45)
  - Tufts Data-Sharing Program, 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 46)
  - Postsecondary Finance and Facilities, 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 47)
  - Blank Forms, 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 48)
  - Bundy Aid, 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 49)
  - Draft Copies HEDS, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 50)
  - Copies of Reports Sent to Us, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 51)
  - Shirley Rubinow's Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 53)
  - HEDS/HEGIS Due Dates, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 54)
  - NYSED--1 Adm, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 55)
  - NYSED--3, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 56)
  - NYSED--5 College and U Libraries, undated (Box 51, Folder 57)
  - NYSED 8 Dir of Off-Campus Locations, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 58)
  - NYSED EEO-6, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 59)
  - IPEDS-- IC, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 60)
  - IPEDS--SA, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 61)
  - HEDS/HEGIS Reports, 1988-1993 (Box 51, Folder 62)
  - Bundy Aid, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 63)
  - Blank HEDS, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 64)
  - HEDS/HEGIS Reports: Due Dates, 1986-1987 (Box 51, Folder 65)
  - HEDS Respondent Completion Forms, 1986-1987 (Box 51, Folder 66)
  - HEDS/HEGIS Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 51, Folder 67)
  - HEDS U Salary Data Exchange, 1986-1987 (Box 51, Folder 68)
  - NYSED--1 Adm Info for FT UG, 1986-1987 (Box 51, Folder 69)
  - NYSED 1.1 Institutional Characteristics, 1986-1987 (Box 51, Folder 70)
  - NYSED 2X.1 Application for Participation--Actual Fig, 1986-1987 (Box 51, Folder 71)
  - NYSED--3 Emp in Inst of HE, 1986-1987 (Box 51, Folder 72)
  - NYSED--5 College and U Libraries, 1986-1987 (Box 51, Folder 73)
  - NYSED--7 Inventory of College and U Physical Facilities, 1986-1987 (Box 51, Folder 74)
  - NYSED--8 Dir of Off-Campus Locations, 1986-1987 (Box 51, Folder 75)
  - IPEDS Form--Inst Char, 1986-1987 (Box 51, Folder 76)
  - ED 2300-4 Fin Stats of Inst of HE, 1986-1987 (Box 51, Folder 77)
  - Tufts Datacom Educom Sharing Project, 1986-1987 (Box 51, Folder 78)
  - Bundy Aid Requirements, 1986-1987 (Box 51, Folder 79)
  - Blank HEDS Forms, 1986-1987 (Box 51, Folder 80)
  - Sexual Assault Prevention Information, 1991-1992 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058577 3
  - Chronological Files, 1993-1994 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - American Universities and Colleges Questionnaire, 1986-1987 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - SED/Continuing Education Program Inventory Survey, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - American Chemical Society Certification Information for Chemists, 1989-1990 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Higher Education Surveys--Survey on UG Education in Geology, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Higher Education Surveys--Survey on UG Education in Physics, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - National Research Council Survey on Funding Sources, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - American School & University Magazine Survey on Compensation, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - College Counsel (US News & World Report) Institution Resource Survey, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Comm. On Independent College & University Fiscal and Economic Survey, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Council for Aid to Education (CFAE) Survey for Voluntary Support to Ed, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Fund for the City of New York Nonprofit Industry Study Phone Survey, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - National Center for Postsecondary Gov & Fin Survey, 1989-1990 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Dept of Ed Applic & Fiscal Operation Report (FISAP), 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Higher Ed Data Sharing Consortium (HEDS) UG Financial Aid Questionnaire, undated (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Association of Research Libraries (ARL) Statistics Questionnaire, 1989-1990 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Association of Research Libraries (ARL) Statistics Questionnaire, 1988-1989 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Association of Research Libraries Quick SPEC Surveys, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - ARL--SPEC Survey on Staff Recognition Award, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Libraries--Miscellaneous Surveys, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Libraries--Miscellaneous Surveys, undated (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - NYPL Compensation Survey, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges Inst. Profile Annual Report, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - USA Today--Campus Safety Survey, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - USA Today--Campus Safety Survey, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Washington University Survey of Judicial Procedures, 1989-1990 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Council for Adult and Experimental Learning, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - CICU Coordination Programs with elementary and secondary schools, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - NYS Ed Dept Math/Science/Technology Program Survey, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - U of Miami Questionnaire on Doctoral Policies, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - Chicago Lighthouse for the Blind, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 32)
  - Survey on Retention Practices of HE Institutions, 1989-1990 (Box 52, Folder 33)
  - International Ed Data Collection Committee--Foreign Scholars Survey, 1989-1990 (Box 52, Folder 34)
  - Lovejoy's Survey on Learning Disabilities, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 35)
  - NACAC Questionnaire--Learning Disabled Programs and Services, 1989-1990 (Box 52, Folder 36)
  - NYS Ed Dept Survey of Services for College Students with Disabilities, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 37)
  - Peterson's Guides--Programs for Learning-Disabled Students, 1989-1990 (Box 52, Folder 38)
  - UNESCO info for study abroad, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 39)
  - NASPAA Doctoral Program Questionnaire, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 40)
  - Peterson's Guide, 1986-1997 (Box 52, Folder 41)
  - Peterson's Guide Annual Survey of UG Institutions, 1989-1990 (Box 52, Folder 42)
  - Peterson's Guide Annual Survey of Graduate Institutions, 1989-1990 (Box 52, Folder 43)
  - Phi Theta Kappa Scholarship Directory Listings, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 44)
  - School District of Philadelphia--Coll/Univ Data Sheets--"VICS 91", undated (Box 52, Folder 45)
  - Science Service, Inc., Survey of Student Science Training Programs, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 46)
  - National Beta Club Information, 1991-1992 (Box 52, Folder 47)
  - Yale News Insider's Guide to Colleges, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 48)
  - Yale News Insider's Guide to Colleges, 1989-1990 (Box 52, Folder 49)
  - GRE/CGS Directory of Grad Programs, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 50)
  - CGS/GRE Survey of Graduate Enrollment, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 51)
  - Peterson's Guide Annual Survey of Graduate Institutions, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 52)
  - Higher Education Surveys, undated (Box 52, Folder 53)
  - College Entrance Exam Board Annual Survey of Colleges, 1989-1990 (Box 52, Folder 54)
  - CICU Campus Profile Survey, 1991 (Box 52, Folder 55)
  - CICU Campus Profile Survey, 1989-1990 (Box 52, Folder 56)
  - Comparative Guide to American Colleges Questionnaire for Presidents, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 57)
  - Custom Databanks Inc. College Major Search System Survey, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 58)
  - Fiske Guide Selective Guide to Colleges, 1991-1992 (Box 52, Folder 59)
  - HEDS Undergrad Admissions Questionnaire, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058583 1
  - Houghton Mifflin Company Guidance Info System, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Jersey City State College Survey of Weekend Offerings, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Jesuit High School Rank in Class Survey, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - MacMillan Publishing Company Questionnaire for College Blue Book, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Masconomet Guidance Survey, 1989-1990 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Mitchell, Robert E. Minority Students Guide to Top Colleges, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Montgomery College Transfer Fact Sheet, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - National Hispanic Institute College Register Info Form, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - NWSA Directory of Women's Studies Programs, 1989-1990 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - NJ Comm Coll Transfer Counselor 4-yr College Transfer Data Sheet, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Orchard House, Inc. Annual College/University Info Update, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Peterson's Guide Annual Survey of UG Institutions, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - College Counsel (US News & World Report) Factoids for Am. Best Colleges, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - College Counsel (US News & World Report) Survey, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - College Counsel--Freshman Admission Survey, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - College Counsel--Stats for America's Best Colleges, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Surveys--Information, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Surveys--Memoranda, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - American Council on Education Survey of Student Assessment Programs, 1989-1990 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - AAU/AGS Project for Res on Doctoral Ed, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Council on International Educational Exchange Study Abroad Programs, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Jamestown Community College Questionnaire on Computer Graphic Art & Design, 1989-1990 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Johns Hopkins Investigation on Ph.D. Requirement, 1989-1990 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - The Modern Language Journal--Doctoral Degrees in Foreign Languages, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - NASULGC Educational Activities in Eastern Europe, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Seminars on Academic Computing, Directory of Computing Facilities in HE, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - State Ed Dept/Higher Ed Data, 1988-1989 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Undergrad Drama Dept Survey for Directory of Theatre Training Program, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Uconn Econ Dept FED Survey on Race and Gender Programs, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - AACRAO Task Force on Revision of FERPA Guidelines, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Equal Opportunity Commission EEOC Report, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Equal Opportunity Commission EEOC Report, 1989-1990 (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - HEDS FTE Calculations and Student/Faculty Ratios, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - NASPAA--Annual Survey, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 35)
  - NRC Survey of Administrators and Faculty, 1989-1990 (Box 53, Folder 36)
  - Peterson's Guides Annual Survey of Higher Ed Personnel, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 37)
  - Peterson's Guides Annual Survey of Higher Ed, 1989-1990 (Box 53, Folder 38)
  - American Career Exploration System Questionnaire, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 39)
  - ACT Grad/Prof School Survey, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 40)
  - ACT Institutional Data Questionnaire, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 41)
  - AAMC Combined Degree Program, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 42)
  - Belmont Hill School Admissions Questionnaire, 1989-1990 (Box 53, Folder 43)
  - Canadian Bureau for International Education SOJOURNS, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 44)
  - Chronicle Guidance Publications, Inc., Survey of Majors, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 45)
  - Chronicle Guidance Publications, Inc., Chronicle College Databooks, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 46)
  - Chronicle Guidance Publications, Inc., Survey of Majors, 1989-1990 (Box 53, Folder 47)
  - College Bound Fall Admissions Trend Survey, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 48)
  - College Entrance Exam Board Annual Survey of Colleges, 1991-1992 (Box 53, Folder 49)
  - Majors List Project, undated (Box 53, Folder 50)
  - National Survey of Post-Secondary Faculty, undated (Box 53, Folder 51)
  - NYU Statistics Form, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 52)
  - Survey Issues, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 53)
  - U.S. News & World Report College Survey, undated (Box 53, Folder 54)
  - U.S. News & World Report, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 55)
  - Surveys--Fact Sheets, Lists, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 56)
  - Human Relations, 1991-1992 (Box 53, Folder 57)
  - Human Relations, 1983-1989 (Box 53, Folder 58)
  - Human Relations, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 59)
  - HR Ratings Committee Files, undated (Box 53, Folder 60)
  - HR Ratings Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 53, Folder 61)
  - HR Background Information, undated (Box 53, Folder 62)
  - New York State Regents Doctoral Evaluation Project: Self-Study Questionnaire for Statewide Review--Psychology, Vol. 1, 1985-1987 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058580 7
  - New York State Regents Doctoral Evaluation Project: Self-Study Questionnaire for Statewide Review--Psychology, Vol. 2, 1985-1987 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Human Relations Registration, 1989-1990 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Human Relations Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Human Relations Site Visit, 1985-1988 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - SED- Sexual Assault Requirements, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058570 8
  - NYSED-2, and NYSED-2A Certification of Degrees Conferred, Estimate of Earned Degrees, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - NYSED-2H Postsecondary Enrollment of Student with Disabilities, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - NYSED- 2R Total Undergrad Inst. Activity, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - NYSED- 2.3 Supplment 1 & 2, Degree-Credit Enrollment by Subject Area, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - NYSED 2.2- F/T Undergrad. Transfer Enrollment, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - NYSED 2.4- Opening Fall Enrollment, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - NYSED 2.4A- Preliminary Degree-Credit Enrollment, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - NYSED 2.7- Noncredit Enrollment, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - NYSED 2.8- Residence and Migration of College Students, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - NYSED 2.9- Graduation Rate Rrport for F/T UG study by racial/ethnic categories, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - NYSED 2.9A- Grad rate report for study in - post op. programs by racial./ethnic, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - NYSED 4.1- Student Financial Aid, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - NYSED 5- College and Univ. Libraries, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - NYSED 7- Inventory of College/Universities Physical Facilities, and Stud. Credt Hrs. Taught, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - NYSED 8- Directory of Off Campus Inst. Locations, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - ACT Grad/Profressional School Survey Form, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - ACT Institutional Data, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Alcohol and Drugs Program- Higher Education Institution, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - American Bar Association, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Best "B" Schools (Business Week), 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Black Issues in Higher Education, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Cambridge Associates: Admissions/ Financial Aid, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Chronicle Guidance Publications (Databases), 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - College Board: Masters and Doctors Programs, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - College Board: Annual Survey of Colleges, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - College Counsel & U.S. News- America's Best Colleges, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - College University Information Update, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Doctoral Programs (Change Magazine), 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Guide to American Graduate Schools, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - GRE/CGS Graduate Program, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - Higher Education Directory, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - International Handbook of Universities, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - Misc Requests, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - Money for College: Guide to Financial Aid for African-American Students, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - Money Guide: Best College Buys, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - NIICU: Survey of UG Students Fin Aid Assistance from Inst Sources, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 37)
  - Pequis Info: National Center for Educational Statistics, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 38)
  - Pequis Info: Deaf in Postsecondary Education, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - Peterson's Annual Survey of Freshman Financial Aid, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 40)
  - Peterson's Annual Survey of UG Institutions, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 41)
  - Peterson's Annual Survey of Graduate Institutions, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 42)
  - Peterson's Directory of Higher Education Personnel, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 43)
  - U.S. News & World Report--Colleges and Universities (Opinion), 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 44)
  - U.S. GAO Minority Scholarships, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 45)
  - U.S. News & World Report--America's Best Graduate Schools, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 46)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University: Request for NYU Tuition, Board, etc., 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 47)
  - HEDS Instructions/Dbase, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 48)
  - HEDS/HEGIS (Bundy Aid), 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 49)
  - IPEDS--EE--IPEDS Early Estimates, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 50)
  - IPEDS--IC (Institutional Characteristics), 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 51)
  - IPEDS--EF1 Enrollment by Racial/Ethnic, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 52)
  - IPEDS--F1 Financial Stats, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 53)
  - IPEDS--R1 Residence of First-Time Students, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 54)
  - IPEDS--SA, Salaries, Ten & Fringe Benefits of F/T Instructional Faculty, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 55)
  - NYSED 1.1- Basic Student Charges, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 56)
  - NYSED 2.1 Suppl Racial/Ethnic Dist for Select., 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 57)
  - Summer Seminar General Info., 1991 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058571 6
  - FRN Summer Seminar Evaluations, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - FRN Post Questionnaires from Scholars, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - FRN Post Questionnaires from Hosts, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - FRN Background on Scholars and Hosts, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - SIR Final Report & Correspondence, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Seminars Final Report, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Seminars Participants, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Seminars Evaluation, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Summer 1991: Responses: A Poetics Workshops (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Responses: The Columbus Legacy, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Responses: American Experience as seen through the African American Experience, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Responses: Advances in Modern Biological Sciences, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Responses: Neurons, Visions, and Cognitions, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Responses: Early American Experience, Mainstream, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - 1991 Summer Seminars Final Report (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - SIR Post Questionnaire Spring 1992 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Pre-Q and Cover Letter, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - SIR Responses, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - SIR Background, mailing addresses, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Summer 92 SIR Info., 1992 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - FRN Expenses, 1992-1993 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - SIR Fall, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - SIR Final Report, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Academic Year 92-93 SIR Report, 1992-1993 (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - FRN General Info, 1992-1993 (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - SIR Summer 1992 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Summer 92 SIR Background Info, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - Summer Institutes Background, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Summer Seminars Final Report, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - Summer Modern Near East Institute, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - Summer Advances in Modern Chemistry Workshop, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 32)
  - Summer Issues for Continuing Education workshop, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 33)
  - Summer: World of 1492 and Ours, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 34)
  - Summer:American Immigrant Experience, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - Summer: Programs, General Background, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - Summer: Education in America: The Dream and the Reality, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 37)
  - SIR, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 38)
  - SIR Surveys, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 39)
  - Ford Foundation, undated (Box 58, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058572 4
  - FRN- Associates F/U, undated (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - FRN- Liaison F/U, undated (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - FRN- Scholars F/U, undated (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - 1985 Surveys (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Suggested change in form, Aug 1985 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - University SIR, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Age of Democratic Revolution, undated (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - F/U Draft- 1988-89 American Constitution, 1988-1989 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - FRN Questionnaires, 1989-1990 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Background Info, 1989-1990 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Assoc. Pre-Q, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Assoc. Post-Q, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Scholars Pre-Q, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Scholars Post-Q, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Evaluation Writeup, 1989-1990 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Summer SIR Evaluation, undated (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - FRN Summer- Harrington Appl, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - FRN Summer- LAX Appl, undated (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - FRN Summer- Peters Appl, undated (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Draft of 1990-1991 FRN Report (Box 59, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058573 2
  - FRN Info., 1990-1991 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - FRN Assoc. Pre-Q Spring, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - FRN Assoc. Post- Q- Spring, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Scholars Pre-Q- Spring, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Scholars Post-Q Spring, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - FRN Questionnaires, 1990-1991 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - FRN SIR:, 1990-1991 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - FRN Associates. Pre-Q- Fall, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - FRN Associates. Post- Q- Fall, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - FRN Summer Seminar Evaluations, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Visiting Scholars- Gen'l Info., undated (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Summer 1990 Info (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - FRN-Grant Proposals, undated (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - FRN- National Science Foundation, undated (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - FRN- General Info, undated (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - FRN Associates Pre- Q- Spring/ FRN Associates Post -Q-Spring, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - SIR Background, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Pre-Ques ad Cover Letter- Fall, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Fall 91: SIR Post Ques and Cover Letter, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - SIR-Pre Ques and Cover Letter, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Post Ques and Cover Letter, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Athletic Restricted Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058579 9
  - Athletic Restricted Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Athletic Income Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Athletic Income Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Athletic Field Budget, 1991-1992 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Athletic Field Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Athletic Field Budget, undated (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Athletic Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Athletic Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - ECRs (January-December), 1993 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - ECRs (January only), 1994 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Academic Program Review Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Coles Athletic Salary Worksheets, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Coles Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Coles Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Coles Plant Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Coles Income Budget, undated (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - AAUP, undated (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Benefits Study Committee Report, 1991-1994 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Centers and Institutes, undated (Box 61, Folder 20)